There are some new trolls on the block.
Trolls Band Together is a animation, family, music film directed by Walt Dohrn.
When Branch's brother, Floyd, is kidnapped for his musical talents by a pair of nefarious pop-star villains, Branch and Poppy embark on a
harrowing and emotional journey to reunite the other brothers and rescue Floyd from a fate even worse than pop-culture obscurity.
Poppy (voice), played by Anna Kendrick.
Branch (voice), played by Justin Timberlake.
Viva (voice), played by Camila Cabello.
John Dory (voice), played by Eric André.
Velvet (voice), played by Amy Schumer.
Veneer (voice), played by Andrew Rannells.
Trolls Band Together is a 2023 American animated jukebox musical comedy film produced by
DreamWorks Animation, based on the Good Luck Trolls dolls from Thomas Dam.
It is the sequel to Trolls World Tour (2020), and the
third installment in the Trolls franchise.
The film was directed by Walt Dohrn and co-directed by Tim
Heitz, and written by Elizabeth Tippet.
Anna Kendrick, Justin Timberlake, Zooey Deschanel, Christopher Mintz-Plasse, Icona Pop, Anderson .Paak, Ron Funches, Kenan Thompson, Kunal Nayyar and Dohrn reprise their voice roles from the
previous films, with newcomers Eric André, Kid Cudi, Daveed Diggs, Troye Sivan, Camila Cabello, Amy Schumer, Andrew Rannells, RuPaul and Zosia Mamet joining the ensemble voice cast.
The film follows Poppy and Branch as they set out in an attempt to rescue their long-lost brother, Floyd, while
also reuniting Branch's estranged brothers after the boyband phenomenon, BroZone, was disbanded.
Ideas for a third Trolls film began prior to the release of Trolls World Tour in April 2020, when
Timberlake expressed interest in participating during his Apple Music takeover.
DreamWorks Animation officially confirmed the third
film's development in November 2021.
Despite being predominantly CGI animation, with some additional animation by DNEG, the film includes some 2D
animation sequences with animation styles inspired by Yellow Submarine (1968) and Fantasia (1940).
Theodore Shapiro returned to compose the score for the film.
Trolls Band Together premiered in Los Angeles on November 12, 2023, and was
released in the United States by Universal Pictures on November 17.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $210 million.
The film explores themes of pop star, brother, musical, sequel, based on toy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.